<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs> 

  <TerrainDef Name="ColourTileBase" ParentName="FloorBase" Abstract="True">
    <texturePath>Terrain/Surfaces/GenericFloorTile</texturePath>
	<designatorDropdown>SterileTilesGroup</designatorDropdown>
    <statBases>
      <Cleanliness>0.6</Cleanliness>
      <WorkToBuild>1650</WorkToBuild>
    </statBases>
    <costList>
      <Steel>3</Steel>
      <Silver>15</Silver>
    </costList>
    <constructEffect>ConstructMetal</constructEffect>
    <designationHotKey>Misc4</designationHotKey>
    <constructionSkillPrerequisite>8</constructionSkillPrerequisite>
    <renderPrecedence>244</renderPrecedence>
    <researchPrerequisites>
      <li>SterileMaterials</li>
    </researchPrerequisites>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>GraySterileTile</defName>
    <label>gray sterile tile</label>
    <description>Gray Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(128, 128, 128)</color>
  </TerrainDef>

  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>BlackSterileTile</defName>
    <label>black sterile tile</label>
    <description>Black Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(35, 35, 35)</color>
  </TerrainDef>  
    
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>LightBlueSterileTile</defName>
    <label>light blue sterile tile</label>
    <description>Light Blue Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(120, 150, 255)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
   <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>BedBlueSterileTile</defName>
    <label>bed blue sterile tile</label>
    <description>Bed Blue Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(114, 149, 166)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>BlueSterileTile</defName>
    <label>blue sterile tile</label>
    <description>Blue Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(80, 120, 255)</color>
  </TerrainDef> 
 
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>LightGreenSterileTile</defName>
    <label>light green sterile tile</label>
    <description>Light Green Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(160, 255, 200)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>BedGreenSterileTile</defName>
    <label>bed green sterile tile</label>
    <description>Bed Green Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(139, 173, 121)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>GreenSterileTile</defName>
    <label>green sterile tile</label>
    <description>Green Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(128, 200, 160)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>LightRedSterileTile</defName>
    <label>light red sterile tile</label>
    <description>Light Red Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(200, 0, 0)</color>
  </TerrainDef> 
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>BedRedSterileTile</defName>
    <label>bed red sterile tile</label>
    <description>Bed Red Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(173, 121, 121)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>RedSterileTile</defName>
    <label>red sterile tile</label>
    <description>Red Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(128, 0, 0)</color>
  </TerrainDef>   
    
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>LightTealSterileTile</defName>
    <label>light teal sterile tile</label>
    <description>Light Teal Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(0, 200, 200)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>TealSterileTile</defName>
    <label>teal sterile tile</label>
    <description>Teal Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(0, 128, 128)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
    
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>LightPurpleSterileTile</defName>
    <label>light purple sterile tile</label>
    <description>Light Purple Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(200, 0, 200)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>BedPurpleSterileTile</defName>
    <label>bed purple sterile tile</label>
    <description>Bed Purple Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(139, 121, 173)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>PurpleSterileTile</defName>
    <label>purple sterile tile</label>
    <description>Purple Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(128, 0, 128)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>LightYellowSterileTile</defName>
    <label>light yellow sterile tile</label>
    <description>Light Yellow Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(255, 255, 0)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>Bed YellowSterileTile</defName>
    <label>bed yellow sterile tile</label>
    <description>Bed Yellow Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(173, 165, 121)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
  <TerrainDef ParentName="ColourTileBase">
    <defName>YellowSterileTile</defName>
    <label>yellow sterile tile</label>
    <description>Yellow Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</description>
    <color>(225, 225, 0)</color>
  </TerrainDef>
  
</Defs>
